{"data":[{"question":"The new information on asbestos caused panic in construction and industry like.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"information ","b":"panic ","c":"in construction ","d":"like","answer":"4","explain":"- Like-> alike","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The weaving design was then embellished with a series of small chained diamond of  vertical and zigzag lines.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"weaving ","b":"chained ","c":"diamond ","d":"zigzag ","answer":"3","explain":"- Diamond-> diamonds","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Aside from the resolution to have more ecumenical conferences,  the most accomplishment of the group was that it met at all.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Aside from ","b":"most ","c":"it met ","d":"at all","answer":"2","explain":"- The most-> the","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The more Robert tried to please his mother through mere flattery, the greater he  succeeded in annoying  her.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"more ","b":"tried to ","c":"the greater ","d":"succeeded in ","answer":"3","explain":"- The greater-> the more","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you know that the population of Washington D.C. is about as many as that of  Minneapolis?      \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the population ","b":"about ","c":"as many as ","d":"that of  ","answer":"3","explain":"- As many as-> equal to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Generally speaking, tax returns must be filed annually, but in few cases they must be submitted every six months.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Generally speaking","b":"annually","c":"in few cases ","d":"every six months","answer":"3","explain":"- In few case-> in a few cases","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"A question often posed about journalism is How much freedom should reporters have interpreting any given news item?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"often posed ","b":"should reporters ","c":"interpreting ","d":"news item","answer":"3","explain":"- Interpretting-> to interpret","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"An analytical index group many individual subtopics under major subject headings.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"group ","b":"individual ","c":"under ","d":"subject ","answer":"1","explain":"- Group-> groups","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Within the Alamo were one hundred and eighty men, more than two thirds of them had recently migrated from near-by states.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were ","b":"thirds of them ","c":"migrated ","d":"near-by states","answer":"2","explain":"- Thirds of them-> thirds of who","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The building opposite to the bank is among the few higher ones that has been put up during the last few years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"opposite to ","b":"the few ","c":"has been put ","d":"last ","answer":"3","explain":"- Has been put up-> have been put up","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"}]}